export default [
	{
		question: "T-minus 30 minutes until your driver arrives. Time to get out of bed and put on spy gear, like the real spy you are. What’ll it be?",
		answers: ["> Business suit and top hat. After all, the smarter you look, the  smarter you’ll act.", "> Sweatpants and a portable charger. Function over form!"],
        messages: ["You don your bulletproof business suit, tailored to your  form for maximum movement. After loading various stun guns, knives, cigars, tweezers, and live birds into your surprisingly large pockets, you put on a snazzy fedora and check your reflection in the mirror. It winks back at you.", "You throw on your sweatpants and hop back in bed. “Set a timer for 27 minutes,” you say to no one in particular as you drift back to sleep."]
	},
	{
        question: "Your driver, Janet, arrives in a nondescript sedan. She may have no style, but at least she drives fast. What music do you ask her to put on?",
		answers:  ["> Skinny Love - Bon Iver: it’s a mood day. Janet understands.", "> Shut Up and Dance - Walk the Moon: nothing gets you more hyped for a big mission.", "> Symphony No. 9 - Beethoven: you have impeccable taste.", "> lofi rap beats to chill/study to: hype is overrated…this will get you in your zone."],
		messages: ["Your eyes well up as you stare out the window, remembering easier times. As you pull up to the Deluxe, it  begins to rain.", "Before long you’ve got Janet singing along with you. As you speed into the Deluxe roundabout with one last flourish, you’re still holding onto that feeling.", "The ride passes uneventfully. You’re too focused on the numerous contingency plans in your head. Before you know it, you’ve arrived.", "You can do special things with the right music. You sink  back into your chair and the world melts away from you,  replaced by cool focus and determination. Soon, you’ve arrived at the Deluxe."]
	},
	{
		question: "You nod to Janet as she drives away from the Deluxe. Okay, time to do the thing. You enter through a revolving door and find yourself in a grandiose lobby, bustling with people. Now…how to find Dr. Disinfo?",
		answers: ["> Threaten the concierge.","> Find a quiet corner and contact your agency HQ.","> Try to hack into the hotel’s database","> Slide a bribe to the bellhop"],
		messages: ["You walk up to concierge and casually reveal the stun gun in your waistband. “Where’s the Doctor?” you say, quiet enough so only she can hear. She pales. “He-He’s on the top floor. In the penthouse.” You make for the elevator.","Your call is picked up almost immediately by the promising young intern. He reveals they’ve just received some intel: Dr. Disinfo is on the top floor, in the penthouse. You thank him and head for the elevator.","Using your smartphone, you go through a backdoor into the hotel database and access the directory, which is, frankly, not very well protected. You quickly discover Disinfo’s location: penthouse suite, top floor. You make for the elevator.","You walk up to the bellhop and flash a winning smile.  “Where’s your boss?” you say slyly as you flash a crisp $100 bill. He narrows his eyes, then extends a hand and takes the money. “He’s on the top floor,” the bellhop says, pocketing the bill. “In the penthouse.” You nod and make for the elevator."]
	},
	{
		question: "The elevator opens with a DING! and you walk in. Just as the doors are closing, a shifty looking guy in a trench coat squeezes in. The elevator begins to rise and he clears his throat. “So, uh…how ‘bout the weather?” How do you respond?",
		answers: ["> Casually put your earbuds in and smile politely. Something smells fishy.", "> “Oh BOY! That is a fanTAStic question!” you say, laughing and slapping your knee. “If only we knew…”", "> Cock your head to the side and glare at him coldly. “How ‘bout it?”", "> “The real question,” you say with a smirk, “is whether pineapple belongs on pizza.”"],
		messages: ["He repeats his question. When you continue not to respond he glares at you, sighs, and straightens his coat. ","“Very well, agent. I see we will need to do this the difficult way.” Intimidated, he leaves the room to find some guards as backup.","He looks at you uncomfortably. “Alright then, jeez” he mutters under his breath.","At the mention of pineapple on pizza you see him recoil ever so perceptibly, then recover quickly. “Not quite my thing,” he says in a slightly stiff voice. “Always thought it might…make me sick.”"]
	},
	{
		question: "Just as you’re about to reach the top floor the elevator grinds to a halt. He cracks his knuckles and shrugs off his coat, revealing a very stylish Dr. Disinfo-brand T-shirt. How do you respond? ",
		answers: ["> Back up against the wall and subtly press the open doors button","> He doesn't seem like such a tough guy. You can take him. "],
		messages: ["He walks closer, sneering at you. Then suddenly the doors open and you dash out, just beyond his outstretched arm. He follows, but you deliver a well-placed kick to his stomach, knocking him back into the elevator as the doors close. ", "You drop into a crouch as he throws his first punch, which slams into the wall right where your head should have been. You duck under his next punch, then counter with a well-placed elbow to his chin. He drops cold. You open the doors and exit to the hallway."]
	},
	{
        question: "The hallway in front of you looks empty. At the end, you see what is clearly the entrance to the penthouse, emblazoned with Disinfo’s logo above the doorway. Do you… ",
		answers: ["> Slip into an alcove to survey your surroundings?","> March boldly towards the penthouse."],
		messages: ["You slide into the shadows, making yourself as  inconspicuous as possible. As you settle into your  position, you don’t notice a figure slowly emerging from the corner behind you…BAM! You crumple to the floor. ", "This is a great idea in theory. Unfortunately, you’re too distracted by your passing reflection in a mirror to notice the guard approaching from behind…BAM! You crumple to the floor. "]
	},
	{
		question: "You wake bound to a table under harsh light. Dr. Disinfo emerges from the darkness, clapping slowly. “Well done…well done, agent! I knew it was only a matter of time before you showed up. For I am irresistible! Unobtainable! Indigestible!” After a moment he nods confidently to himself. How do you respond?",
		answers: [ "> “Please sir,” you say innocently. “I don't know anything! I was just here to deliver a pizza!”", "> Remain silent. He’s good, boy oh boy is he good. But he’ll  never break you.", "> Flash your most seductive smile.", "> Subtly whisper to your smartwatch, calling in reinforcements."],
		messages: ["He lets out an evil — and clearly well-rehearsed — laugh. “Mwah-hah-hah-hah…hah…hah…hahhhhhhh. You think you can fool me, agent? Think again.”", "The smile falls off his face, replaced with a sneer. “Very well, agent. I see we will need to do this the hard way.”", "He blushes slightly. “You know, agent, despite all the times you’ve meddled with my plans I always thought we had a chance.” Then he shakes his head. “But I know better than to fall for your tricks one more time.”", "“Don’t think I didn’t see that!” Disinfo exclaims. He takes the watch off your wrist and puts it in his pocket, shaking his head in disappointment."]
	},
	{
		question: "Just then, Disinfo’s aide enters the room and bows deeply: “Brunch is served, your evilness.” Disinfo’s stomach growls and he rushes from the room. Now’s your opportunity to escape! You’ve got some options.",
		answers: ["> Strain against your bonds. Surely your arms of steel are strong enough to break them! ", "> Survey the room for something to help you escape. ", "> Reflect on the poor choices that brought you into this situation.", "> Call for the guard dog to bring you the keys"],
		messages: ["With a mighty tug you break the leather straps! Freedom at last! ", "Your eyes fall upon a classy Disinfo-brand pen on a  nearby nightstand. Rocking your table, you manage to slowly move across the room until you can reach it with your fingertips. After a few seconds wiggling it in the lock, you’re free.", "In your contemplation, you realize that the restraints are slightly too big for your slim wrists. With a little work, you manage to wriggle your hands free. A moment later, your legs are free too.", "You’ve seen enough movies to know there’s usually a guard dog with keys. Magically, a guard dog appears with a gleaming silver key, placing it delicately in your palm. You’re free."]
	},
	{
		question: "You jump off the table, looking around to find yourself in Disinfo’s control room. What kind of villain keeps hostages in his control room? On the desk is a single vial of clear liquid, suspended in a matrix of lasers. This must be the poison. Do you…",
		answers: [ "> Go to the control panel? There must be a way to disable the lasers.", "> Back out to the nearest exit. You smell a trap."],
		messages: ["As soon as you touch the control panel, alarms go off everywhere. Oops. Wincing, you glance one last time at the vial before running for the exit. It’s time to get out of here!", "Sure enough, as you step away from the table you trip a wire and alarms start going off everywhere. Darn that Disinfo! You run for the exit. "]
	},
	{
		question: "You sprint out of the penthouse and can hear the footsteps of Disinfo’s guards close behind. Quick: pick a way to escape!",
		answers: ["> Climb into the vent system.", "> Bust out a window.", "> Take the elevator reading “DR. DISINFO’S PRIVATE ESCAPE ROUTE, DON’T USE UNLESS YOU’RE DR. DISINFO.", "> Go find the henchman you knocked out: you need a disguise."],
		messages: ["You pull out your pocket knife and pry open the grate to reveal a dark tunnel. Swallowing, you begin to crawl. It sounds like someone’s following you, but eventually you reach another grate and push it open. You’re in the Deluxe lobby.", "CRASH! Glass shatters at your feet. Just as you’re about to drop down your rappel line, a guard sees you. She stares at you, confused. You raise your index finger to your lips. “Shhhhh”. You wink and disappear out the window.", "The elevator opens, revealing a chair with a seatbelt. You strap in and press the down button, feeling your stomach lurch as the elevator suddenly drops. Within seconds, the door opens to the hotel lobby.", "Near the elevator, you find him still passed out and quickly take his Dr. Disinfo-brand T-shirt. Emerging unrecognizable, you walk right past a confused Dr. Disinfo and take the stairs down. An enraged scream behind you makes you pick up the pace."]
	},
	{
		question: "You make it to the exterior of the hotel where there are plenty of vehicles by the curb, each with a Dr. Disinfo insignia. Time to pick your getaway vehicle.",
		answers: ["> A slick matte black Aston Martin.", "> A plain van that probably has some really high-tech stuff in it.", "> A dashing red convertible with chrome highlights.", "> A low-profile Prius"],
		messages: ["“I’m sorry,” you whimper as you brace your elbow and smash through the glass. Climbing through the window you pop open the dashboard and hotwire the car.", "Lo and behold: the trunk is adorned with screens of all sizes, each flooded with lines of code, technical readouts, maps, graphs, and apps. Even better: the keys are in the ignition. It’s your lucky day.", "You slide across the hood of the car like a freakin’ badass and hop into the driver’s seat. Popping open the dashboard below the steering wheel and connecting two red wires, you hotwire the car.", "Ah yes, the mark of a true agent. You pop open the dashboard below the steering wheel and connect the two red wires, hotwiring the car."]
	},
	{
		question: "As you begin to drive away Dr. Disinfo appears and launches himself onto the hood of your car. Looking at the steering wheel you see a shiny red button right in the center. Dr. Disinfo screams “DON’T YOU DARE DO IT!” You don't know what it does. Do you press it?",
		answers: ["> Yes", "> No"],
		messages: ["With a winning smirk you look straight at Dr. Disinfo and press the button. A rumble. You can feel the vehicle transforming around you. “NO!” Dr. Disinfo screams, holding even tighter to the hood. Wings slide out on either side of the car. The wheels fold in, locking into position as the vehicle rises off the ground just a few inches. You floor it. Dr. Disinfo loses his grip and you shoot into the sunset, leaving him a tiny speck in your rearview. ", "You smirk at Dr. Disinfo and slam on the gas. Your vehicle screeches out of the hotel roundabout, swerving left and right to shake him off. Bit by bit he slips off until he’s just hanging on by his fingertips. “This is just the beginning” he says, just before  falling off the hood. You peel out into traffic, leaving Dr. Disinfo behind on the pavement."]
	}


]